razorgator.com 2015-04-29

# Razorgator Tickets Privacy Policy & Security | Live Event Tickets

PRIVACY POLICY

As a Razorgator.com client, you are in control of all your event planning as well as your personal information. As the leader in our industry, we realize that earning and retaining your trust is of paramount importance, so protecting your privacy is a responsibility we take very seriously. 

That's why we've provided this Privacy Policy which sets forth our policies regarding the collection, use, and protection of the personal information of those using Razorgator.com. Personal information means information that can be linked to a specific individual such as name, address, telephone number, email address, and credit card number. 

We encourage you to review and familiarize yourself with our Privacy Policy, but be assured that we do not sell or rent our customers' personal information to third parties. If you have any further questions or concerns, please contact us at 310.481.3400. 

Some of our marketing partners use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.razorgator.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

Razorgator   
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact the Privacy Team at 4094 Glencoe Ave. Suite A, Marina del Rey, CA 90292.

Special note about children   
This site is targeted primarily for use by adults. We do not currently market to or create special areas for use by children. Accordingly, we do not knowingly collect age identifying information, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13 years. However, we hereby advise all visitors to our site under the age of 13 not to disclose or provide any personal information on our site. In the event that we discover that a child under the age of 13 has provided personal information to us, in accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (please see the Federal Trade Commission’s website at www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy for more information about this Act), we will delete the child’s Personal Information from our files to the extent technologically possible. 

Personal information gathered by Razorgator and how it’s used   
When browsing our site, you are not required to provide any personal information unless and until you choose to make a purchase or sign up for one of our email newsletters or other services, as described below. We do not knowingly permit the site to be used by any person under the age of 18 and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children (meaning those younger than 13 years of age). A valid credit card is required to make a purchase on our site. 

Making a Purchase   
In order to purchase tickets and related services through our site, you must provide us with some personal information such as your name, your credit card number and expiration date, your credit card billing address, your telephone number, and your email address. If you are making buying tickets for one or more people other than yourself, you will need to make sure that each of these other individuals agrees, in advance, that you may disclose their personal information to us. 

Customer Registration   
If you choose to become a registered customer of Razorgator, you must provide your email address, password, and password validation. This information is collected on the registration form for several reasons including: (i) personal identification; (ii) to complete air, hotel, car, and other reservations; (iii) to allow us to contact you for customer service purposes, if necessary; (iv) to customize the content of our site to meet your specific needs; and (v) to make product improvements to our site. In addition, we need your email address to confirm your new customer registration and each ticket you transact on our site. As a Razorgator customer, you will also occasionally receive updates from us about ticket sales in your area, special offers, new Razorgator services, and other noteworthy items. However, you may choose at any time to no longer receive these types of email messages. 

Customer Profile   
As a Razorgator customer, you can choose to complete your online profile by providing us with event preferences, credit-card billing information, delivery address, and other personal information. This information is used to assist you in purchasing tickets quickly without having to type in the same information repeatedly. If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page, /tickets/members/login. You may also contact us via email at rg-sales@razorgator.com or call 800.542.4466 to speak with a representative. 

Partners   
We use third parties to provide news, packages, and logos on our site. We do not share any personal information with these companies. If you choose to purchase a package from our partners at PrimeSport, any information you provide them is subject to their privacy policy. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. 

Online Surveys   
Razorgator values opinions and comments from customers, so we frequently conduct online surveys. Participation in these surveys is entirely optional. Typically, the information is aggregated and used to make improvements to Razorgator and to develop appealing content, features, and promotions for customers. Survey participants are anonymous unless otherwise stated in the survey. 

Promotions & Sweepstakes   
Razorgator frequently sponsors promotions and sweepstakes to give customers the opportunity to win Hard-To-Get® tickets and related prizes. We collect and maintain personal information about you through the operation of these promotions and sweepstakes in order to enable us to provide you with the best service. We also collect personal information for other activities that include contacting you, conducting survey questions, collecting other marketing data and other uses detailed throughout this privacy policy. From time to time, marketing emails will be sent to your email address provided upon entry into the promotion or sweepstakes. We use contact information to notify contest winners and survey information to develop promotions and product improvements to the Razorgator.com web site. 

If the promotion or sweepstakes is conducted in conjunction with a celebrity, any personal information we obtain through the promotion or sweepstakes may be shared with the celebrity or the agency who promotes the celebrity. For example, if we run a promotion endorsed by celebrity “X”, your name and email address would be shared with the agency who promotes celebrity “X”. 

Before entering a particular promotion or sweepstakes, you should first refer to its Official Rules: /tickets/sweepstakes-terms-conditions/. 

We only collect personal information that is voluntarily provided to us. You can opt-out of receiving promotional emails, or otherwise sharing your personal information, by following the steps detailed below in the privacy policy. 

Automatic Logging of Session Data   
We automatically log generic information about your computer's connection to the Internet, which we call "session data," that is anonymous and not linked to any personal information. Session data consists of things such as IP address, operating system and type of browser software being used and the activities conducted by the user while on our site. An IP address is a number that allows computers, such as our web servers, know where to send data back to the user via the internet, such as the pages on the site that the user wishes to view. We collect session data because it helps us analyze such things as what items visitors are likely to click on most, the way visitors are clicking through the site, how many visitors are surfing to various pages on the site, how long visitors to the site are staying and how often they are visiting. It also helps us diagnose problems with our servers and lets us better administer our systems. Although such information does not identify any visitor personally, it is possible to determine from an IP address a visitor's Internet Service Provider (ISP) and the approximate geographic location of his or her point of connectivity. 

Cookies   
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. There are many myths circulating about cookies, but you should know that cookies are only read by the server that placed them, and are unable to do such things as run programs on your computer, plant viruses, or harvest your personal information. Razorgator uses cookies to help analyze our web page flow, to measure promotional effectiveness, and to foster trust and safety. 

First and foremost, you can rest assured that no personally identifiable information ("PII") about you (e.g., name, address, etc.) is gathered or stored in the cookies placed by the Razorgator.com web site and, as a result, none can be passed on to any third parties. 

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies. Of course, by changing the options on your web browser or using certain software programs, you can control how and whether cookies will be accepted by your browser. Razorgator supports your right to block any unwanted internet activity, especially that of unscrupulous websites. However, blocking Razorgator cookies may disable certain features on our site and may make it impossible to purchase or use certain services available on the site. Please note that it is possible to block cookie activity from certain web sites while permitting cookies from sites you trust, like Razorgator. 

General information Razorgator collects and why   
“General Information” is information about you or your activities on our site that do not identify you personally. When you use the internet, your web browser or software may communicate certain information to the host website you visit. Examples, of General Information include the unique number assigned to your server or Internet connection, the capabilities and features of your computer, you geographic location, and your movement and activity within a particular website. Likewise, when you register as a customer of Razorgator, enter certain sweepstakes and promotions, or complete offers like email newsletter subscriptions, we collect general information about you such as age, gender and zip code. We collect and store this information to generate statistics about visitors to our site for non-personal demographic purposes. 

How long your personal information is kept   
We generally keep user data on our server or in our archives for as long as we reasonably need it. We may alter this practice according to changing requirements. For example, we may delete some data if needed to free up storage space. We may keep other data for longer periods if the law requires it. In addition, information posted in a public forum could stay in the public domain indefinitely. 

Data management requests are administered in an orderly manner to the extent feasible and within our direct control. Please note that we have greater control over recently collected data than over archived data. Once data is removed from the system and archived, it may not be feasible to accommodate specific requests. In those cases, our general data retention policy applies. 

Opting out of promotional emails   
At any time, you can unsubscribe from our Get The Edge or other newsletter or similar services through the "My Account" link, accessible on the Razorgator home page. 

As a customer or promotion/sweepstakes entrant, you will occasionally receive email updates from us about ticket sales in your area, special offers, new Razorgator services, and other noteworthy items. We hope you will find these updates interesting and informative. Of course, if you prefer not receive them, please click on the "unsubscribe" link or follow the instructions in each email message or by sending a letter: 

Attn: Marketing Department   
Razorgator, Inc.   
4094 Glencoe Ave. Suite A   
Marina del Rey, CA 90292 

Razorgator reserves the right to limit membership to those who will accept emails. Customers will be notified via email prior to any actions taken. 

Protection against the misuse of customer information   
Razorgator contains links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another website for which Razorgator has no responsibility. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of all such sites as their policies may be materially different from this Privacy Policy. Of course, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and your Razorgator membership account information. Please be very careful, responsible, and alert with this information, especially whenever you're online. In addition to the circumstances described above, Razorgator may disclose client information if required to do so by law, court order, as requested by other government or law enforcement authority, as requested in connection with any governing entity regulating ticket distribution to any event or in the good faith belief that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable including, without limitation, to protect the rights or properties of Razorgator or its affiliated companies or when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities. Further, if Razorgator or substantially all of its assets are acquired, our customer information will most likely also be transferred in connection with such acquisition. 

In addition to the circumstances described above in the previous paragraph, Razorgator is obligated to collect and provide certain personal information in connection with the sale of any World Cup Ticket for each attendee of a World Cup Event. Specifically, FIFA Federations, Sponsors, the 2006 FIFA World Cup Organizing Committee - Germany, and other venue sponsors regulating ticket and event venues for the World Cup in Germany in 2006 require that each attendee of a World Cup Event provide the following information with respect to each ticket user: (1) name, (2) date of birth, (3) nationality, as shown on attendee's passport, and (4) passport identification number. Accordingly, as a condition to delivery of tickets purchased for any 2006 World Cup event, this information must be provided for each ticket user as part of the checkout procedure, or Razorgator will be unable to deliver the World Cup tickets to you. Please also note that the personal information you provide about each ticket user will be maintained in the United States for processing and dissemination to the governing bodies that require it. 

Changes to the Privacy Policy   
This policy is effective as of January 1, 2005. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

If you have a privacy question or concern   
Of course, you may always submit concerns regarding our Privacy Statement or our privacy practices via email by clicking here. Please reference the privacy policy in your subject line. Razorgator will attempt to respond to all reasonable concerns or inquiries within five business days of receipt. You can also write to us in care of Razorgator, 4094 Glencoe Ave. Suite A, Marina del Rey, CAa 90292 Attn: Privacy Team. Agents 

We use an outside shipping company to fulfill orders, and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes. 

Service Providers   
We use Cybersource to provide credit card transactions on our site. When you buy tickets, we will share billing information as necessary for Cybersource to provide that service. Cybersource is prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. Thank you for using Razorgator! 

Security Guarantee

Razorgator guarantees the safety of your online purchases 

We are so confident that your credit card transaction will be secure that we back every online purchase made at Razorgator.com with our Shop Safe Guarantee powered by Payment Tech, the nations largest processor of e-commerce and direct marketing payment transactions. Razorgator uses the latest in encryption technology to ensure that every transaction is safe. 

Our Shop Safe Guarantee   
In the unlikely event that an unauthorized use of your credit card occurs, follow the reporting procedures defined by your credit card provider and contact us at sales@Razorgator.com immediately. Most credit card companies cover all charges that result from unauthorized use of your credit card or may limit your liability to $50.00 US - the maximum liability allowed under the Fair Credit Billing Act. For additional information on the Fair Credit Billing Act, contact the Bureau of Consumer Protection or visit the Federal Trade Commission web site at [www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/). 

Technology   
Our secure server software encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card information. The process of encryption takes the information you enter and converts it into bits of code that are securely transmitted over the Internet. This scrambled data cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet. 

Once your encrypted personal information is received by our secure server, it is translated back into its original form and stored in our off-line database. Your credit card information is not transmitted over the Internet again. To further ensure the safety of all your personal information, we've located our off-line database in a secure underground data center. 

Credit Card Security Desk   
If you are more comfortable with inputting your credit card number over the phone, you can call or fax our Client Service Center with your credit card information: In the United States, call 800.542.4466 or fax to 310.289.3010. Outside the United States, call 310.481.3400 or fax to 310.289.3010.
